Mission 6: The brave rush into Plum Blossom Villa
You say I'm not MAN enough?
You don’t look at a mirror before you’re out for a movie
Hey, wake up!
Don’t be too enchanted by my singing…
We’re at Plum Blossom Villa now
It’s not even my turn yet to fan you
Subs by oofvegetable (and translators in our awesome Discord server :D)
Don't steal our subs in any way (You know who you are)
Have we arrived yet?
It’s right up there
Time flies in happy times…
how about
At last, let me sing you another school song
“You drooled on your desk during the lunch nap”
no no no
no need, great swordsman,
leave that for the next time
We’re in a hurry
Mr. nine-fingers
Actually, we run a hair salon
If you ever decide to hold a concert
and you need a new hairstyle,
feel free to reach out to us!
Thank you for bringing us all this way
Bye bye!
Hold on a second
This is…
It's a fruit basket!
I heard you were looking for that girl called…
Plum Blossom something
It’s Plum Blossom Thirteen.
This place is called Plum Blossom Villa
Meeting her parents, eh?
Guessing it’s your first time?
Nononono
You can’t just show up empty handed!
At least bring some fruits, eh
and a chicken too!
It's all about giving them a good first impression
Good morning uncle
My name is Wu Liuqi.
even though I'm not that much of being economically stable,
But I'm going to try my best!
You really took it as meeting the parents...
Hello there,
Is there anyone home?
It’s an automatic door?
You scaredy cat!
automatic my arse!
It was me who pushed it open
Come in then!
Wouldn't this be too impolite?
Uncle, hello!
My name is Wu Liuqi.
These fruits and this chicken,
just a little something!
No way
Dachun…?
Have we…
come to the wrong place?
We’re here
This is Plum Blossom Villa
Right,
My name is Plum Blossom Eleven.
This used to be my home.
Right now,
its forcibly occupied by a cranky old man!
They went too far!
I’ll go teach them some manners!
I’m here to retrieve a certain something of mine
But
That old guy’s swordsmanship…
is really, really good
You may lose your life if you’re not careful enough
It’s not too late for you to regret right now
X
First code of the Bodyguards’ handbook!
Once you accepted a task,
never retreat!
Take it.
You’re my bodyguard.
From the moment we enter through this door,
No matter what happens,
You must still protect me
Subs by oofvegetable (and translators in our awesome Discord server :D)
Don't steal our subs in any way (You know who you are)
This is the place
It’s you again…
Lucky that the Villa’s owner isn’t here today
otherwise,
he’s going to kill you!
You’re that
squatting, white haired old man?
I want to teach you some manners.
The white haired old man I was talking about…
that’s not him.
He…
is just the housekeeper.
I apologise,
mister housekeeper.
I don’t really care if he’s here or not.
I’m just gonna go inside to grab my stuff.
This place…
doesn’t have a damn thing that’s yours
Indestructible Virgin Body?
This girl’s cruel and ruthless
The last time she’s here, she harmed our young master.
这次又要来偷东西
And now… you’re here again to steal!
Listen up pentagon face,
if you insist on protecting her,
then don’t put the blame on me if I use excessive force.
Do you trust him,
or do you trust me?
No. 5 of Bodyguards’ Handbook—
Shut up.
Seems like we have to defeat him first.
Wait a sec.
That shirt… it's very very expensive!
Skywards pillar: The ONE
I’m poking your eyes!
Mount Tai is weighing on me
Too insidious!
Solid As Gold: Seven Day Lock!!!
We can’t defeat him!
I’ve got him locked
Go get your things, quickly!
You're dead!
金金
金刚
金刚不坏
Solid as gold,
也要运功才能使出来的
It take some effort to dish out the attack.
If I repeatedly attack your temple,
there’s no way you can dish out the attack move!
Damn it,
He really can’t deal out attacks invincibly anymore!
Go quickly!
Bodyguard Handbook…
Irrelevant—
I TRUST YOU!!!
There’s no way around it.
I’ve got to use THAT technique.
Subs by oofvegetable (and translators in our awesome Discord server :D)
This… isn’t this the long lost “Rope of Divinity” of the martial underworld?
Once you’re tied up,
there’s no way you can exert force!
You broke ass looking doorkeeper
how can a low life like you own a contraption like this…
You think an old geezer like me
can defend the entirety of this huge villa?
What do you think I’m relying on?
What do I think you're relying on?
You, shut up!
That wasn't a real question!
But… Rope of Divinity
It will also drain your Qi…
It’ll stop working immediately once you let go
Release her, now!
Release me first;
only then will I consider it.
Solid as Gold: Seven Day Lock - This move of mine…
I must stay locked for seven days before I can let go
Who the hell thought of
such a boring move?
So that's the situation.
So that's the situation!
On the one hand, we’ve got Dachun and Thirteen’s sister,
For sure I'm going to be on their side!
But I can’t just go and beat up her Mr. Majordomo…
cause we’re going to live altogether in the near future.
Then you just sneak over there,
cut the rope, and it’ll all be fine.
Okay!
You know, the weather’s so cold up here…
So why’s everyone wearing clothes
like they’re still on Chicken Island?
Qi Controlled Scissors!
I Cut!
Give it up!
Once you’re tied up,
You can’t do anything
It’s up to you, Dai Bo!
Such strong qi!
The owner’s back.
How could he sense it before I did?
What good weather!
Subs by oofvegetable (and translators in our awesome Discord server :D)
Waiting… will tomorrow be a sunny day?
Waiting for yesterday, I’m no longer afraid of those memories
I miss u
Scattered with dark emotions
The you in my memories
Decided to go on a trip on your own
Insisted on going on the trip alone
decided to go on a trip on your own
Meet
It’s not even in summer
Good weather where the sun shines through…
like we’re destined to part ways
The “you” I’m missing
full of the warmth of positive emotions
Wishes that you will end your travels
wishes that you will end your travels
Let’s meet again
even if the weather is bad
and we don’t need to fuss over things again…
Who needs to separate from each other? :D