Forever obey the leader
These trash…
It’s been so long and you all still haven’t caught Green Phoenix’s apprentice.
The longer she lives on,
the more my unease grows.
You, go out and spread the news for me.
Green Phoenix…
is being kept captive in Crocodile Valley of Blackrock Mountain.
Yes, sir!
You all should know what to do.
We will set up a webbing trap to capture her,
we won't ever fail!
My injury
has almost fully healed by now.
It’s just that… I’m still not fully ready to lay down my heart.
I’ve arranged for someone to come with you.
He’s the newest member of the Shadow Killers.
Killer number: Nine.
Actually, I can handle it by myself.
What if that guy
has already recouped all of his powers?
Would you still be able to defeat him?
You mean killer number Seven?
“That” was nothing but a failed experiment.
Is his blade
as quick as mine?
I’m just kidding!
There’s no need to be so serious.
I don’t like this guy.
I don’t either.
Bro got that "fire in the hole" ahh in him
Wait a second.
Why am I being locked up?
Because we trespassed onto private property
and attacked their housekeeper.
You were the one who attacked him!
I brought a fruit basket and a chicken!
I even knocked on the door!
False accusation!!!
Let me out!!!
Otherwise, I’ll pee here wherever I—
Any louder and I’ll cut your tongue off and serve it with a cup of wine!
But the doctor told me my body is overtly “humid,” not to mention that my tongue has a thickly white coating…
Tongues don’t taste very good!
(Ox tongue does taste really good, it's chewy and got a mild, subdued meaty flavour since its pure muscle)
Nonsense.
Living by the sea will obviously result in high body humidity levels.
Is that so?
I have a medicinal tea recipe that could help with that.
If you give me a pen,
I’ll write it down for you.
You two…
I didn’t expect you to also know about Chinese medicine.
Why are you two so annoying?!
Indestructible Virgin Body!
I didn’t even say anything…
Why shoot me?
Wait!
I actually just have one tiny request.
I just want to
meet up with Plum Blossom Thirteen.
NOT GONNA HAPPEN!!!
YOU WANNA PICK UP GIRLS?
Well, I won't let you! I’m enough to stop you from flirting with her!
YOU’RE GONNA STAY SINGLE FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE!!!
He confiscated my scissors,
but I still have another blade.
Go, go!
Go up!
That old man
never thought I would still—
So, it’s you…
Not him, not him.
No, no you’ve got the wrong guy.
Then, take a look at this scene.
Doesn’t it feel a bit familiar?
I built this place to be exactly the same as it was back then.
All to figure out the answer to
why, back then,
I failed.
But
isn’t this sculpted a little too ugly, though?
I’m not a professional sculptor!!
Hold up,
that’s not even the important point!!
But from my memory,
I don’t recall you at all.
Well, do you recall a
suave and personable young man in there?
I do indeed recall a handsome guy,
but what connection could you have to him?
He’s me!
In the past,
I used to be a man of equal beauty and wisdom who captured people with nets.
I collected money from people
and captured them with my nets!
Never have I failed!
I was known as:
Divine looks, worthy of the Rope of Divinity!
I understand!
But anyways, for now, you’re
Plum Blossom Villa’s
Mr. Anti-theft security net!
I’m the great Mr. Majordomo here…
Don’t interrupt!
I’m not done speaking!
Two years ago,
I constructed what I thought was the most perfect net trap I had ever made.
But that fish
still broke out of it.
That was the one and only time I failed.
In this line of work,
one failure
and your present facade must disappear off the face of the Earth
to avoid retribution.
Your own failure
shouldn’t be blamed on others!
If it wasn’t for him
escaping from the net
and remembering my face,
then I wouldn’t have needed plastic surgery.
I changed my body shape,
and changed my voice.
But plastic surgery
doesn’t necessarily have to make you look uglier.
I DON’T CARE!!!
I MUST ONCE MORE
CHALLENGE YOU!!!
You scared me!
I thought you wanted my handsome face
Who the hell want such an ugly face?
Let me lay down the rules!
Why is it me again?
The rules are very simple:
you just need to save this chicken,
get to the exit
and you win.
However,
if you get caught in my Rope of Divinity,
then it counts as a loss for you!
If you touch that corporeal beast,
you’ll also be electrocuted to death.
If you win,
I’ll even let that potato go.
Potato? Where?
But if I win,
then the knot in my heart will untie.
And this place
will have no need to exist.
And all of you here will
disappear along with it.
Dai Bo!!
Seven!!
I forgot to tell you just now
I swapped out your blade.
I wanted you to use it less, you know.
It’s exactly the same as before, as expected!
I’VE CAUGHT YOU!!!
X
Goodbye.
I failed again.
No matter how many tries
would it still end in failure?
But he seems
so much weaker than before.
Hey, I’m not free yet.
Get lost!
Why did I still lose…
Help untie a bit of the rope
The one you want to bind is my past self.
Forget about him.
It’s all in the past.
It’s all…
in the past…?
You’re no longer a capture net.
You’re Plum Blossom Villa’s premier housekeeper.
Thirteen’s already gone.
I don’t know where she went either.
She’s been like this since she was a kid.
So stubborn.
Always eager to get ahead,
even when she clearly needs help
She doesn’t know how to ask for it, either.
No problem.
I’ll be able to find her.
See you later!
I failed my mission to protect you again.
Full refund.
I apologize!
But I don’t want your refund.
I only wanted to get my own stuff back.
Then, let’s try again.
Why don’t you even ask me
what I’m going to fetch?
What are you getting?
Forget it.
It’s something from past times, after all.
It’s the people in front of me
that are alive and well that are far more important.
I don’t see anyone in front of us.
The people in front of us,
where are they?
Where’d she go?
How did you fall down there?
Today is yet another
粘粘阳光的新早晨
new morning with bits of sunlight
Friends! Who’s still deep in their dreams?
Lazy bums! Why aren’t you awake?
Today, I got to change into a suave looking T-shirt too
I’m going out with full spirit
Riding my humble motocompo
taking a slow drive around my community
The bad tempers of yesterday
let me tell you about it all
All those troubles
will be forgotten today
I want them to accumulate in me, no more
the secrets of summer
Occasionally, the aroma of Durian breezes by my nose
Kitten, let’s play!
Happy emotions
encircles the community
There’s something new everyday
Happy emotions
surrounds the community
There’s something new everyday
We got it every year
Fresh new uploads
Finally found you
You think you can hide in here for a long time?
If you want us to fight,
we got to change places.
The place can be any of your liking.
I will never lose to you for the second time!
Seven, he's playing serious this time!
Everyone, come and watch the ensuing battle here!