Is it raining?
My brother
why don’t we change seats?
What do you want?
We’re on public transport, travelling by Qi-controlled sword!
If you don’t like squeezing in here, just go sword-riding yourself!
But, it’s not that crowded here…
I just like to sit like this
Come at me if you dare!
You… Hm!
People like you who take the sword,
I’m sure your Qi and internal forces mastering, if any, are quite embarrassingly bad
Dai Bo, there’s no need to, no need at all.! Don’t…
Just put away the weapon first…
We’re almost arriving at the interchange
Those who are going to get off the flying sword, pack your bags!
get ready *Ad Space for rent* *Final stop: Plum Blossom Villa*
This is a Skysword Interchange.
Passengers who need to change swords,
please exit your sword.
For passengers who are in no need of a change of routes,
please wait on the sword
Line No. 4 is ready to depart.
May passengers sit down and hold on steadily
So cold…
That Plum Blossom Villa that you are going to…
is in northern Xuanwu
The region is high in altitude
It’s only natural for temperatures to lower as you go further north
Sir, can’t you start up the central heating?
Is there hot water there?
Give me some
It’s ok now
So many disparaging comments when you’re literally taking public transport
Two cents
And i will open up or a windshield.
Sure thing, sure!
About the windshield…
Woah… my body’s all warmed up now…
Thumbs-up Kung Fu guy, it’s you!
What a coincidence,
didn’t expect to bump into you right here
It’s fate!
Eh? These injuries on your body, how did you-
It’s all because he saved you
He took damage from fighting that rock guy…
You must not have known about this… you were unconscious at that time
Just look at how he’s all bruised up and injured
He must have lost the fight
It’s hard to say though…
Yeah, a loss, you shouldn’t put it that way…
He was chagrined by what you said
Turns out it’s all because he saved me
Dai Bo, act fast and take out the meds and give-
Let’s fight!
Huh? Did I hear wrong?
Us… are you talking about us? A fight between us?
You heard it right!
I want to fight you, one on one!
Let’s fight to the death on this very sword!
A battle between life and death
Even if I don’t quite understand…
But I’m in a rush to save someone
Why don’t you wait for me to finish saving her
And then we catch up later at some other place.
Right, you’re right!
I’ll prep some wine pairings by then, let’s catch up later
You Shadow Assassins have killed countless of people
how is it possible for a SHADOW ASSASSIN, of all people, to save lives?
From your Kung Fu…
It seemed like it… Are you the successor to the Thumbs-up Fist?
Your master died under his blade
You should be hating him
Go take your revenge on him…
but you’re so weak
It’s impossible for you to beat him,
It’s more than enough for you to let me see just how good you are at Thumbs up style
Say, why don’t we make it like this:
Let’s wait for the sword to stop
Get off it and fight on the ground?
Someone is fighting on your sword!
Don’t you care at all?
Ha… It happens just about everyday
You guys fight all you want,
just don’t interfere with my sword control
Hey hey hey!
Don’t mess with my control,
don’t mess with it!
My hat, gimme back!
I’m finished!
Seven!
Stop with the fighting
We almost caused it to rollover
I dodge
I duck
Another dodge,
And another duck
You got to listen to my explanation first
Shadowless foot jab of Buddha’s Mountain!
My waist is almost broken…
Here I come!
I saw that
Thumbs-up Kung Fu is a fighting style which attacks after your opponent strikes
If you don’t strike,
Then I can’t beat you
Once you start attacking me,
I will give you a thumbs up in return!
Isn’t that fantastic?
Six times seven equal 42 stances...
Thumbs-up!
There are two idiots fighting on the sword!
Really… These people think they have lived just way too long
When they fall, you probably can’t even find their corpse!
Let’s have a fight of thumb-ups!
Maybe this way, I can recover my lost memories
Three years ago
A Stanian appeared in Xuanwu,
our mission was to kill him.
But your master intervened and stopped it,
And helped out with his escapade
Your master's nothing but a traitor of Xuanwu
Even after I broke his bones,
he would not hand the guy over.
My master isn’t a Xuanwu traitor!
I will seek justice for him!
You’re too weak.
You can never avenge him
Driver, look out for the road!
Please hold your attacks
We’re in due course for a collision into the mountain!
Ah… Hey hey hey hey
Don’t come over here!
Ah sh*t, we crashed
He was..
Saving people?
Xia Fei, I thought you are injured?? Can you still fly?
*looney-tunes ahh fall*
You still want to fight?
My master said
You can look into one's heart
based on the way of his fist
Even if it’s the same fist fighting style,
It will feel different per person
It all hinges on the one using it
So while crossing fists,
You can have a rough impression of their character
So, just what kind of person
do you think I am?
You do not seem like a bad person
Me, however.
The Thumbs-up Fist I was using
was filled with hatred and anger
I was like a beast,
totally unbecoming of the Thumbs-up Fist.
If my master saw how I was just now,
he must have been really disappointed in me
I still could not recall
the everything that had happened
But based on the little memories I retained,
I have to admit, I definitely crossed fists with your Master
What?
Are you dying to ask
what could possibly be the reason I told you all these
It’s all because
I wanted more people to know the notions of the Thumb-up Fist
In the future, before any of you want to strike first,
you would think it through a little
When my enemy doesn’t strike me,
neither will I
This world,
will have lesser conflict!
Oh, and,
He’s really an amazing Martial Artist.
I promise you
Once everything is over,
I will come back and look for you
Of course!
we have not decide a winner on
just who has the better Thumbs-up Fist?
Next time, why don’t we compete in our hairstyling skills?
hahahaha
Even at the cost of your life, you would still protect that Stanian.
…unless, in actuality, you're a spy?
Not everyone from Stan is a bad person,
either way, people from Xuanwu are not all saints
Thumbs-up Fist,
Advocates for the love for life
and cherish sentience
regardless of borders,
Regardless of race
Whenever I see someone who is in need of help,
I will definitely lend a hand
Such good weather
Waiting… will tomorrow be a sunny day?
Waiting for yesterday, I’m no longer afraid of those memories
I miss u
Scattered with dark emotions
The you in my memories
Decided to go on a trip on your own
Insisted on going on the trip alone
decided to go on a trip on your own
Meet
It’s not even in summer
Good weather where the sun shines through…
like we’re destined to part ways
The “you” I’m missing
full of the warmth of positive emotions
Wishes that you will end your travels
Let’s meet again
even if the weather is bad
and we don’t need to fuss over things again…
Who needs to separate from each other? :D