Mission 3: The return to Xuanwu
Hmm…? There isn’t much of a difference at all
Stick out your tongue
hmm... a little too moist in there
I’ll prescribe you with some meds
eight bowls of water, simmer into one.
normally, avoid drinking ice-cold water
It was ME who helped removed the poison from your body
remember to treat me to a meal later
Ah! My beer D:
What a waste. What a waste…
Erm… “This” you got…
Have you…remembered.. anything from your past?
Let me try
Umm. Which elementary school did I go to?
Umm.
Nope. Can’t remember anything at all.
Nope. Not even my secondary school.
Seven
This doesn’t make sense
The poison has already been cleared out of your system
Take this. Try to recall how you used this weapon in the past.
Gosh! I’m seeing some terrifying things!
Yup, seems like he’s fine now.
The remnants of poison in your body has been fully purged.
It’s just that the memories from your past have been forgotten for a long period of time.
You need a little something to bring those memories back
As long as you come into contact with objects and people from your past,
your memories will slowly come back
it’s just like playing with a jigsaw puzzle.
So, once he starts gaining back his memories,
would there be any change to his persona…
Hey, hey! Seven, seven!
Chicken Island is all safe now
We’ve already beaten up White Fox!
You can rest assured and go rescue Ms. Assassin in peace
It’s time for a different shot
Come over here for your anti-inflammatory jab!
Handsome! Let me tell you what happened.
The other day, there’s this guy who showed up on Chicken Island
He makes things go boom.
But I’ve crushed him!
No need to praise me.
Ye ol trusty stabby never dulls!
Oh, oh let me send you a photo.
Seems like Chicken Island is all safe and sound now.
So do you want to get going?
Eh? What’s everyone looking at?
Hmm? That’s some sharp senses
He managed to detect the incoming enemy’s presence earlier than I did…
You’re not from Superpower Country,
what are you even hiding for?
I’m kidnapped by people who wore something similar.
Who knows if they’re here again to take me to somewhere else?
We need to bring back a few kids with superpowers back to experiment with.
Once we’re done with the experiment, they will be brought back.
I’ll go back with you.
It’s not like I have been to Stan for a holiday before,
do I need to be handcuffed?
Come~ Get me~ Come and get me~
A quick scan have shown that
the few of you don’t have any Superpower electrowaves in your body
you guys are not from Superpower Country.
That's not always the case.
The adults in Superpower Countries are useless
The younger they are, the stronger their abilities.
As they grow older, their abilities become mediocre.
We only need to grab that one child.
His body contains a very strong level of Healing-type electrowave.
Help me!
Still not fighting back?
RELEASE OUR ARCHMAGE!!
Gigantamaxed Conch… Drill!!!
All of these people are your enemy!
They must die!
[Three Point throw]
[SCORE!!!]
Enough.
Scaring them off is enough
They are all your enemy.
Stanians must die!
Think.
If you kill them now
and then you leave this place forever
in the end the ones who end up suffering,
won’t it be the Superpower people?
You need to keep your head
Um, don’t.
Seven.
I think I saw something with a very strong murderous aura over there
Let’s not go out for now
Seems like I’ve saved a demon.
You got to learn how to control yourself,
Handsome.
Let me teach you
It seemed to be just a very normal leg move.
Why would there be such a devastating power to it?
Claw of the dragon!
See? I can do two-part attacks too!
Turns out he can even control his sword like that!
Golden Iron Palm!
(nah tried my best on this TL)
You have such a formidable power.
What is it for?
Once you own this unparalleled power,
what would you do with it?
Just to kill?
If you were to truly show off how strong you are,
you would use it to SAVE people!
With such strong powers,
It would be really easy to turn into something diabolical.
What’s hard, is not losing yourself to evil.
I’ve used too much energy just now to heal you.
I have to act fast now and use my ultimate ability.
The Supreme Dragon Emperor: Heaven and Earth!
As for the path that lay before you
It all hinges on your choices
Miss Mei,
did you just rub your hand on salted fish?
See, He’s awake now.
I told you this will work like magic.
If it wasn't for the fact you just saved someone,
I would've killed you already!
I’m sorry about hurting you.
It’s nothing.
How could you ever be able to hurt me?
I literally let myself be slashed twice by you, on purpose!
What about that sword?
It’s best that you don’t ever use it again.
What you have is simply just a mortal shell of flesh and blood.
Your body had gone through so many serious injuries.
It’s already quite weak
That sword is no ordinary weapon
It belongs to a class of its own sorts: “The blade of evil spirits”
When you use it, it will rapidly absorb your body’s Qi,
causing irreversible damage to your body.
Based on your body’s current condition,
you will be able to only sustain it for short fights.
Uhm… What if..
Just in case…
What if it’s a really dire situation,
and I have no choice but to use it?
Usage should never exceed a minute.
Say, you can use it for just about another three to five times.
Then, what if he use it more than that number?
He will die.
You should be on your way to Xuanwu now
also, it's about time for you to search for the answer you are looking for.
Here, I’ve got a pouch.
*Marvellous!*
When you are in absolute danger, open it up and take a look at the items inside.
It might be able to help you.
Heh, heh, heh, heh…
We meet again, my little fat chicken…
We have specially bought a new batch of weapons, just waiting for you.
Brothers, please accept this small gift of mine.
You aren’t allowed to lift your fingers!
Young hero, let’s have some tea altogether when you're free!
Da Bao, who’s usually all proud..
He did all this for me–
Thank you, Da Bao
You got the help of the Evil Spirit.
Naturally, you have to pay a huge price for it.
Once you deal with everything, go and return the sword back to its original place.
That’s if you want to lead a peaceful life
Miss Mei,
I really hope you are all safe and sound.
Someone claimed that they saw her up in the North.
I think she’s heading towards a place called Plum Blossom Villa?
Uhm…Excuse me…
Border Passenger Terminal
No. 4: Plum Blossom Villa
No. 1: Valley of Demonic Serpents
No: 27: Plaza of the Divine Condor
Buy your ticket here.
Then, you go up there to take a Skysword.
Skyswords leave every hour!
The exclusive information network transmission right of this work is owned by Aha Entertainment (Shanghai) Co.