I’m already out of time.
In the north of Xuanwu,
there’s still one man
who can teach you.
Master,
I still can’t do it.
Interesting…
It’s been seven years…
Is this it?
Not bad.
But you got your practising all wrong. Double the effort for half of the result.
Let’s go home.
Miss Mei!
That ought to be her father!
Hello, uncle!
My name is Wu Liuqi.
This chicken and these fruits
are my, uh,
… Just a little something for you!
I didn’t want to appear disrespectful.
Is he your friend?
…No.
Given your disposition,
there’s only two reasons for you to be looking for me.
First, to challenge me.
Second, to ask a favour of me.
From the looks of your motioning so far,
it would be the latter.
This was my last resort.
You used two different sword styles today.
Akimbo Flow champions flow in strength and excels in its ferocity.
Qingyun Style: Its moves doesn't betray its namesake, Flowing Clouds and Water.
It is the very embodiment of natural, unrestrained flowing svelte.
But all you’ve got is a mere imitation of them.
You haven’t grasped their essentials—
as if you were only taught of it recently.
Try piercing the boulder in front of you.
Now, look at the ground.
Every time you make a move,
you expel precious Qi everywhere.
At first thought, it seems like an impressive show of might.
However, it is in fact indicative of one’s lack of control over Qi.
In a duel between swordmasters of the best of the best,
that would be your fatal flaw.
And as for this newly learned sword style of yours,
the most vital part is
the “how” in terms of controlling your Qi.
only use it for dealing a fatal strike.
And in an instant,
all of it can be released.
Before releasing it,
your body should be as calm as the surface of water.
But within your body
there lies a huge amount of energy.
Owner!
There’s a very terse situation.
Owner,
I saw some assassins lying in ambush outside.
I think they’re here because of that girl.
Should I…
Just look after the young lord, it’s enough.
Mere assassins…
They’re not worth my attention.
Thank you.
My matters,
I’ll deal with them myself.
(My life my rules ahh)
You have to stay alive a little longer.
I still need to come back to properly challenge you.