Heard you were looking for me
Come to Chicken Island for more info!!!
Seven's special mission: 1
Have you
seen that helmet-shaped spaceship?
Your mission...
is to find a way to sneak inside that thing,
find that door,
and rescue the guys trapped inside it
What about the key?
It's also inside,
you need to go find it yourself
Are we going to the mission together?
Wear this,
then I can see what you see
I'm better off staying,
giving you orders here
Then shouldn't there also be a hi-tech plane
that take both of us to the spaceship?
Actually, we can use explosives or something...
Why not just bomb the hell out of that thing?
The shockwaves will make this entire thing implode.
By that time, Chicken Island will be no more
Just stick to the plan...
Don't sweat it,
I did say I would protect you from harm...
I was lucky,
and thanks for nothing for your "protection"
Your age: ???
This question... it's a bit difficult...
Your age,
you don't even know it yourself?
Anything that happened over 2 years ago...
I can't remember...
According to my calculations...
say, 30?
Eh... maybe some people just don't age as well...
Lemme guess... You're actually an 18 years old kid
*loud incorrect buzzer*
It must be 20
25!
28...
This will be the last time I trust you...
If there's one more time of this...
It opened
Don't open
The door's at the end of this corridor,
Same shit... It's those Infra-Red whatever, useless traps all over again
Not a problem for me, and never will!
I'M SPEED
What a save!
Guess I really didn't expect that...
Again?!
Likes eating: BEEF OFFAL
Calling: Cheap Life Hua
How do you even pass this level?
I saw all that
This door
isn't the one at the end of the corridor
it's actually THAT one...
the one with a lid...
Just open the lid
and you get to enter the next level
And you...
Just speed over there as quick as you can,
go press the start button on the wall...
and the lasers will stop shooting you
There's poisonous gas
I can't open it...
Isn't this Klotski?
That woman...
move her to the square at the bottom,
only then will the door open itself
Isn't this way too hard
Left
Right.
Right
Push, push down
Not this one
Yeah, this one
Now push up
Move that one in the right to the left
Did I forgot to...
cover my nose and mouth?
I can't take it anymore...
I got poisoned...
hey hey hey don't sleep
you're literally one step away,
just push it down
Cheap life Hua? It's over...
Is this... like a fridge?
According to the previous patterns...
This should lead me to the next level...
And... I can't open it.
Let me go check if there's other doors here...
Weird. Looks like there's a dog in the icicle...
Woah. There's a female dog right there
The hairdresser's new mission:
Pet grooming!
Um... I guess it's actually "Pet and frisbee" now...
Maybe I can use some help from it to access the next level...
Hi~
You stupid dog~
You come at me
Come over here
NO WAY IT'S THE BRIDGE
Why... why does this all seem so familiar?
This
This is...
Do you know why this door is locked?
Are you sure you want to open it?
Eh... I told you I will shield you
You should have made the move way earlier,
when you literally are the powerful guy...
It doesn't work that way
My Kung Fu can't harm him.
To defeat him once and for all,
you ultimately need to rely on yourself
What even is this thing?
Don't sweat those details
Direct your focus on it, no hesitations!
My pair of scissors can't even damage him
I need to use his sword!
Cheap life Hua!!!
If you forget the EVERYTHING of the past
Perchance you can start off a new life on a clean slate
Go draw a clear cut boundary from your past
Open the door
and you will plunge yourself straight back into the bottomless pit of darkness,
until death seperates you from it
Don't go back on yourself, when you've already decided your fate
That really tired me out...
I feel like dried Ginseng
Come and have your meds
But I'm naked...
I'm not sure if viewers want to see me in my bday suit...
Clothes are over there
Nice herbal soup
He always sported a nonchalant look
Not much of a looker, he doesn't seem to have any abilities
He doesn't say much either
about big truths
But sometimes, just sometimes, he seems unusually obstinated
The past that can't be removed
it's all for moral's sake, he protects those things that's valued most to him
Close your eyes
Concentrate
Leave anytime
Leave immediately
Don't hesitate even if it's only you that's headed for it